<resources>
    <string name="app_name">The 30 Days of Breakfast Ideas App</string>
    <string name="day_1">Day 1</string>
    <string name="breakfast_day_1">Smoky Bacon, Potato and Cheddar Hash</string>
    <string name="description_day_1">With melty cheddar cheese, crispy bacon, and golden russet potatoes, our breakfast hash recipe will be your new favorite breakfast!</string>
    <string name="day_2">Day 2</string>
    <string name="breakfast_day_2">Baked Eggs with Swiss Chard and Green Olives</string>
    <string name="description_day_2">Cooked in warm cream studded with chard and buttery green castelvetrano olives, this stunning baked egg recipe is an easy and luxurious way to enjoy brunch at home.</string>
    <string name="day_3">Day 3</string>
    <string name="breakfast_day_3">Salsa Verde Baked Eggs</string>
    <string name="description_day_3">Baked eggs in salsa verde are our low stress/no mess way to prepare eggs for one or for many. Sprinkled with cotija and cilantro, and served with warm tortillas these are a fabulously easy meal.</string>
    <string name="day_4">Day 4</string>
    <string name="breakfast_day_4">Spinach-Mushroom Strata</string>
    <string name="description_day_4">Melty Swiss cheese and buttery mushrooms sautéed with fresh thyme make this savory, earthy spinach strata recipe your new weekend brunch-at-home favorite.</string>
    <string name="day_5">Day 5</string>
    <string name="breakfast_day_5">Shirred Eggs with Leeks</string>
    <string name="description_day_5">Like all egg recipes, shirred eggs are pretty quick and easy to make, but they\'re elegant enough for Christmas morning!</string>
    <string name="day_6">Day 6</string>
    <string name="breakfast_day_6">Soft-scrambled eggs</string>
    <string name="description_day_6">As far as we’re concerned, if you know how to make perfectly creamy, fluffy soft-scrambled eggs, you’ve got the skills you need to succeed—in the kitchen, in love, in life. We’ll show you the way.</string>
    <string name="day_7">Day 7</string>
    <string name="breakfast_day_7">Migas</string>
    <string name="description_day_7">Searching for a simple and flavor-packed breakfast? That’s easy. Meet migas, aka the best Tex-Mex breakfast ever.</string>
    <string name="day_8">Day 8</string>
    <string name="breakfast_day_8">Huevos Rancheros</string>
    <string name="description_day_8">Runny, fried eggs over a bed of seasoned beans, atop a layer of warm corn tortillas, add a few condiments and voila! Homemade huevos rancheros!</string>
    <string name="day_9">Day 9</string>
    <string name="breakfast_day_9">Avocado, Chèvre and Bacon Omelette</string>
    <string name="description_day_9">Avocado, chèvre and bacon are the very best omelette filling on the planet, and that’s what we’re here to talk about today.</string>
    <string name="day_10">Day 10</string>
    <string name="breakfast_day_10">Granola with Figs, Almonds and Coconut</string>
    <string name="description_day_10">Homemade fig granola—aka the unbelievably delicious alchemy that happens when you combine oats, honey, and oil with some handfuls of chopped nuts and dried fruit.</string>
    <string name="day_11">Day 11</string>
    <string name="breakfast_day_11">Apple and Maple Baked Oatmeal</string>
    <string name="description_day_11">Sweetened with just a kiss of maple syrup, this healthy apple baked oatmeal recipe is the ultimate fall breakfast.</string>
    <string name="day_12">Day 12</string>
    <string name="breakfast_day_12">Nuts and Seeds Granola</string>
    <string name="description_day_12">This nutty, seedy, maple-sweetened granola makes mornings way easier. Serve it over Greek yogurt with honey and fresh berries for a power-packed breakfast the whole family will love.</string>
    <string name="day_13">Day 13</string>
    <string name="breakfast_day_13">Overnight Oats</string>
    <string name="description_day_13">Overnight oats are the easiest breakfast recipe we know of—just a few minutes of work before bed means that you get to wake up to a healthy + fruity breakfast that’s ready when you are!</string>
    <string name="day_14">Day 14</string>
    <string name="breakfast_day_14">Six-Ingredient Breakfast Quinoa</string>
    <string name="description_day_14">Vegan, high-protein and low-effort, this easy recipe for breakfast quinoa is everything we want breakfast to be. Top it with fresh berries and call the day kicked off!</string>
    <string name="day_15">Day 15</string>
    <string name="breakfast_day_15">Norwegian Risgrøt Rice Porridge</string>
    <string name="description_day_15">Risgrøt—a festive Norwegian rice pudding—is a heart-warming, soul-satisfying treat that is humble, almost too easy, and impossible not to love.</string>
    <string name="day_16">Day 16</string>
    <string name="breakfast_day_16">Sour Cream Coffee Cake</string>
    <string name="description_day_16">Moist and tender, with a coconut-speckled crumb topping, this sour cream coffee cake is easy, delicious and—bonus!—can easily be made gluten free.</string>
    <string name="day_17">Day 17</string>
    <string name="breakfast_day_17">Mom\'s Zucchini Bread Muffins</string>
    <string name="description_day_17">Zucchini bread walks the tightrope between indulgence and healthy treat, and this recipe—which can be made into zucchini muffins or loaves—yields the most moist, tender zucchini bread of all.</string>
    <string name="day_18">Day 18</string>
    <string name="breakfast_day_18">Gingerbread loaf</string>
    <string name="description_day_18">This gently spiced gingerbread cake is topped with fluffy cream cheese frosting and studded with candied ginger and just a hint of orange, making it the perfect holiday treat!</string>
    <string name="day_19">Day 19</string>
    <string name="breakfast_day_19">Banana Bread with Maple Mascarpone</string>
    <string name="description_day_19">We started with our very favorite homemade banana bread recipe and we made it even more decadent by topping it with sweet, creamy maple mascarpone.</string>
    <string name="day_20">Day 20</string>
    <string name="breakfast_day_20">Baked French Toast</string>
    <string name="description_day_20">What if you could make your French toast (or at least most of it) the night before? This cinnamon-y baked French toast recipe is your favorite brunch treat’s bread pudding-ish cousin.</string>
    <string name="day_21">Day 21</string>
    <string name="breakfast_day_21">Banana Pancakes with Caramelized Bananas and Toasted Pecans</string>
    <string name="description_day_21">Banana pancakes with caramelized bananas and toasted pecans—aka definitely a sleep-in, pretend-it’s-the-weekend kind of treat.</string>
    <string name="day_22">Day 22</string>
    <string name="breakfast_day_22">Coconut French Toast with Apples and Pecans</string>
    <string name="description_day_22">Nothing says good morning quite like a plate of warm soft French toast. This particular dish is piled high with poached apples and pecans. Perfect for fall weekends.</string>
    <string name="day_23">Day 23</string>
    <string name="breakfast_day_23">Trail Mix Pancakes</string>
    <string name="description_day_23">Fuel up for a day on the trails, lounging around the campsite, or even just hanging out in your own backyard, with these just-indulgent-enough, protein-packed trail mix pancakes.</string>
    <string name="day_24">Day 24</string>
    <string name="breakfast_day_24">Almond Poppyseed Pancakes with Cherry Syrup</string>
    <string name="description_day_24">With a subtle crunch, a smooth nuttiness, and sweet cherry syrup you’ll want to eat on its own, our poppy seed pancakes offer a fun, tasty twist on a tried-and-true breakfast classic.</string>
    <string name="day_25">Day 25</string>
    <string name="breakfast_day_25">Breakfast Egg Muffins</string>
    <string name="description_day_25">These make-ahead bacon and cheddar egg muffins with jalapeños are a low-carb, protein-loaded treat that you can eat on the go.</string>
    <string name="day_26">Day 26</string>
    <string name="breakfast_day_26">Feta-Spinach Breakfast Egg Muffins with Sun-Dried Tomatoes</string>
    <string name="description_day_26">These baked breakfast egg cups are easy to make, full of iron and protein, and ensure that even the busiest day gets off on the right foot.</string>
    <string name="day_27">Day 27</string>
    <string name="breakfast_day_27">Sausage and Cheese Breakfast Egg Muffins</string>
    <string name="description_day_27">For a healthy breakfast on the go, our sausage breakfast egg muffins—which get a Mexican-inspired kick from Tillamook 4-cheese shredded cheese—cannot be beat!</string>
    <string name="day_28">Day 28</string>
    <string name="breakfast_day_28">Oat Scones</string>
    <string name="description_day_28">Buttery and made moist thanks to a secret ingredient, these oat scones are a Scottish-ish riff on everyone’s favorite breakfast treat.</string>
    <string name="day_29">Day 29</string>
    <string name="breakfast_day_29">Cardamom Rolls with Almond Glaze</string>
    <string name="description_day_29">Generously and warmly spiced, this cardamom roll recipe yields fluffy, tender, rich cardamom buns that will brighten even the dullest of winter mornings.</string>
    <string name="day_30">Day 30</string>
    <string name="breakfast_day_30">Dairy Free Cinnamon Rolls</string>
    <string name="description_day_30">These tender, gooey, dairy-free (!!) cinnamon rolls, are so delicious, no one will know that they’re vegan. Cinnamon Rolls with a Thick Maple Glaze? Yes, Please.</string>
</resources>
